Hey, welcome back!
My name is Sylvia Russell and today we're going to show you how to pick a hair color.
First things first, always consult a professional.
Now I know some of you at home don't trust professionals with your hair.
So make sure to read directions on any box that you picked up from the grocery store.
Make sure to compare your hair color with the color on the box.
This is very important, okay.
So here we have a color ring and this is what I use when I'm deciding on a color for my client.
I give them the option to pick a color, and then, we can also place it against her to make sure that the color we choose will complement her skin tone.
Now, this is something that you may not be able to do with a box of color from the grocery store, but, in your local beauty supply store, you maybe able to pick up a color ring yourself.
So make sure that you pick the right color for you.
The next thing is once we pick a color, we make sure that we agree on it.
So make sure it's something that you really want.
Remember, read the directions, if not, you can't do it yourself at home, consult a professional.
I'm sure she'll give you the color that you love.
Make sure to take a few pictures to give her an idea of what you want.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can pick a hair color.